{"data":[{"question":"In 1849, after graduation from medical school, she decides to further her education in Paris.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"after","b":"from","c":"decides","d":"further","answer":"3","explain":"- Decides-> decided","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Ever since humans have inhabited the earth, they have made use of variety forms of communication.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"humans","b":"inhabited","c":"use","d":"variety","answer":"4","explain":"- Variety-> various","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Body language transmits ideas or thoughts by certain actions, either intentionally nor unintentionally.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"transmits","b":"certain","c":"either","d":"nor","answer":"4","explain":"- Nor-> or","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"It is believed that when a she-wolf loses her litter, she seeking a human child to take its place.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"believed","b":"when","c":"seeking","d":"to take","answer":"3","explain":"- Seeking-> sought","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1925, he joined the advertising department of Doubleday Page and Company, one of the most large publishing houses in New York.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"joined","b":"advertising","c":"the most","d":"houses","answer":"3","explain":"- The most large-> the largest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"He was a favorite contributor to many leading magazines, and her name became a household word.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"favorite","b":"leading","c":"her name","d":"became","answer":"3","explain":"- Her name-> his name","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"We were sitting quiet by the side of a lake when we had an unpleasant surprise.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sitting","b":"quiet","c":"side","d":"unpleasant","answer":"2","explain":"- Quiet-> quietly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"If you are planning to transfer, remember that you must to obtain the permission before leaving the university where you are currently studying.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to transfer","b":"to obtain","c":"leaving","d":"where","answer":"2","explain":"- To obtain-> obtain","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"You must complete the form I -538, have it to sign by the foreign student advisor at the school where you are currently studying.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"complete","b":"to sign","c":"at","d":"currently","answer":"2","explain":"- To sign-> signed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"As more women in the United States moved up the professional ladder, more are finding it necessity to make business trips alone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As","b":"women","c":"professional","d":"necessity","answer":"4","explain":"- Necessity-> necessary","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}